To sum
up, there are four things you need to remember.
Firstly, there are two types of multiple choice
questions.
Multiple choice questions with a single answer and
multiple choice questions with multiple answers.
For this question type, remember that distractors are
often included in the given options.
Therefore, your task is to identify which information
is correct and which may distract you from
the correct one.
Number two, please note that the options might
not come in order as the information
in the recording.
Therefore, you should be quick and focused.
While listening, please move your mouse cursor or
pen to the option being mentioned.
Number three, when you listen, remember to take
notes next to the options.
And the last thing is to always check
the answers and never leave your answer sheet
blank.
In case you totally missed the answer to
a question, just randomly choose an answer if
it is a multiple choice question with a
single answer.
However, the one with multiple answers, choose the
answers based on the question's requirement.
If the requirement asks you to choose two
answers, but you choose three, then you will
not receive any points, even if two out
of those three are correct.
I hope that you will work hard on
this question type and achieve your desired score.
See you in the
next video.
Goodbye.